Gathering 100 coins out here
would be an exceedingly difficult task.
However, we've had the realization
that we can search for the fallen ship,
and we've already figured out its location.
We are weak. But they
cannot take our wits from us.
This game exposes people for the fools they are.
Betraying one another. Murdering one another.
The people here are so determined
to see their base desires realized
that they transform themselves into monsters.
But we are not fools.
And we will not live like vile monsters.
Do not forget this.
Whatever power may
become ours, we are humans,
and we are here to end this meaningless game.
It looks like someone
was fighting here recently.
And they didn't hold back.
This is...
I knew it... They're hiding something!
Huh?
Is this marking off turf?
So there's another team on the other side, huh?
Yes.
Right, that guy did mention that.
When we fought Sanbe,
we stumbled into someone's turf.
That must be why he showed up.
I think this was put here as a warning.
If you pass this mark, you'll be attacked.
But the fallen ship is
on the other side of this.
If we can reach it, we'll gain
a huge advantage over this team.
In other words,
us continuing straight on is bad for them.
Are you crazy?
They wouldn't have put this up here
if they didn't think they could win fights!
Why would we go at them?!
What are you all touchy for?
Is something bothering you?
Wha--?!
Give him a break, Clair.
Huh?
That's enough. Ikeuchi, show them.
Okay.
Ikeuchi scouted out some
of the dangerous territory.
Their turf spreads out west of here.
Hmm, you went in that deep all alone, huh?
I'm surprised you made it back.
Of course I did!
It looks like there are a lot of them.
Ah, okay. These guys, huh?
You said your sister's name was... Elena?
Maybe they were the ones that fought here.
So, what do we do?
We are only after the coins.
I want to avoid pointless fights.
It'll make the trip longer,
but we'll go around this mountain.
Right. I'm sure any group that uses
a symbol like this is full of creeps, anyhow.
Ikeuchi, watch our perimeter.
Huh?
We're going to be relying
on your abilities from here on in.
Okay, leave it to me!
Thanks. I'll be on the lookout for scents, too.
Psh. Do whatever you want.
Are you okay?
Thanks!
We've still got a lot of ground to cover.
Don't push it too hard, okay?
Okay.
Are you okay?
Sorry.
It's fine.
Let's take a break.
Wow! I didn't know you could do that too, Isao!
Heh heh!
This is so good!
I wish they were chilled, though.
You're on your third already? You eat so fast.
You're just slow.
Stop trying to get cleavage shots.
Wha--?!
Say what you will, she's not bad.
You brought her here, after all.
It's nice to take a break, huh?
Want one, Ikeuchi?
I've got a job to do here.
We're going to need you up ahead, too.
You're going to get worn out
if you're on alert the whole time.
He's right.
I guess I can take some.
They're pretty laid back.
Nothing has even happened yet.
You're eating the watermelon, too.
I just need the calories.
Still... Stuff like this is important.
We're a team now, after all.
That's it...
I've got to tell everyone...
Tell them someone has
already gathered 100 coins.
--Umm--
--We should get back on the trail.
It's okay. It's safe up ahead.
What, you don't trust me?!
Sorry, you just can't be too cautious up here.
This route is dangerous. Let's turn back.
Why? The map says we're on track.
I don't see anything in my lens!
We found another team's mark back there, right?
Yeah! That's why we're going
around their turf now!
The turf is the problem.
What is the reason to claim turf out here?
It's to keep coins from being
picked up by other gatherers.
But don't you think that's weird?
That mark was in front of a
steep slope covered in dark forest,
but it's not that far from this open riverbed.
Which place is better for finding coins?
It might be easy to see coins here,
but it's just as easy to see us
and our surroundings.
What if that mark isn't for claiming turf...
What if the mark... is actually there
so that weaker gatherers avoid it
and get herded into this area?
If it is a trap...
We might not be the only ones with wits up here.
What'll we do?
We do have some distance between us, but...
They have numbers.
Calm down, we're fine. We might be weak,
but we're good at getting away.
Oh, they're running away. Did they spot us?
Six, seven, eight. We've got numbers on them.
We might lose a couple on our side, though.
You guys really are idiots.
You think it's okay to let
your friends die like that?
We just need to capture one of them.
Capture one, and treat 'em real nice...
Then, the others will gradually
fall in line and help us gather coins.
All right, I got this!
Little speed demon...
This way!
No way...
How did he catch us so quickly?!
Get back.
Yaahaa! Did my speed scare you?!
Yes. Most revolting,
you're a very convincing monster.
Shut up, pretty boy. Don't think
I'll play nice just cause of your face.
My speed isn't the only
impressive thing about me.
I think he's stalling.
He's trying to stop us here,
so his friends can catch up.
If that's the case, we might as well...
...get started!
Ooh!
Don't move!
Not bad...
Let's not get too excited, here.
We're not trying to take over the world
or destroy the human race, you know?
What will you do once you've
gathered the coins, you ask?
The answer is so simple,
even a kid could tell you.
It's the same for everyone, right?
You do whatever you want.
As long as you yourself are happy,
that's all that matters.
Hand over your coins, and join us.
If you say no, you're all dead.
Not a bad deal, right?
Let's all have some fun together.
Fucking scum.
Huh? What's that?
Don't give me that shit.
You're all a bunch of monsters, too.
All right, maybe this will
make you want to join us.
Check it out.
Don't take it out of the bag.
It stinks!
That thing is the real deal, okay?
There was a girl that wandered
into our turf, just like you guys...
She refused to join us, and our boss killed her.
Our boss is tough as hell.
He's on a totally different level.
That worked pretty well.
It was gross carrying it around,
but I'm glad I did.
Poor thing.
She was beautiful...
My type.
Did she do something to you guys?
That doesn't matter. I told you:
All that matters is that
you yourself are having fun.
Honestly, I don't really like fighting.
I had to drop out of high school
because of a fight.
I hit someone to protect my friend,
and that guy got injured badly.
That was with my normal human strength.
If I think about what'd happen now...
If I unloaded on someone, as a monster...
No... I was wrong...
He wasn't as intimidating as
other gatherers, so I didn't notice...
But I can tell now...
This guy is... a beast!
I guess it's okay if I unload on you, though!
Hang on! If you touch me, I'll--
Punk!
Leader!
Huh? Speak up!
Sorry, I couldn't hear
what you said. Say it again.
Say it, you piece of shit! Come on!
Huh?! Huh?!
That's enough, Yota.
Sorry. I lost my cool.
No way... He didn't kill him, did he?
Well, it seems like he's still alive.
But honestly, I'm surprised.
I knew we'd get into
situations like this up here,
but I never thought someone would
be low enough to use a corpse as a threat.
Do they think anything is
justified in achieving their goals?
It makes me sick.
I think we have other things to worry about!
We've made it clear we're
not on his side, now what?!
That's not really a problem.
In any case, the fallen ship is up ahead--
we just need to keep going.
Yes, that's right. Let's get moving.
I lost them. And I don't see their tracks.
Hanakawa, can you see them
with your x-ray vision?
They're 500 meters straight ahead.
I can see them, naked bodies and all.
Wow, this is messed up. His jaw is knocked off.
He can't even eat like this.
He was always ugly, but at
this point you just have to laugh!
What do you want to do, Madoka?
What can you do? He got all excited
and ran off by himself like that.
He's no use anymore.
If he's useless, why don't you kill him?
I've always hated him.
Me too. He's a creep,
and he's always acting like an asshole.
You guys really are shit.
Anyone can mess up!
You're all idiots, after all.
As you all know, I'm your boss--
I get the coins and the power!
And that's why I have to show you proof.
Proof that I'm meant to be the boss!
You got that, Morita?
Your pain...
...is my pain!
I will never abandon you...
Even if you're all a bunch
of worthless pieces of shit!
You wait here, Morita.
We'll give them smiles just like yours.
Wow, it's like a barricade.
That's a very handy skill.
We shouldn't have to worry
about them catching up now.
Heh heh...
Let's keep moving. Clair, are you sure
you don't want to get inside Shuichi?
It's hot in there. After a while,
I need to get out and--
It was you, huh?
You're the one who did that to my little Morita!
I'm your man!
Shuichi!
What the hell...? Who is he?!
Hey... Don't ignore me!
Hey!
Stop, Yota!
Hey... What the hell are you?
"Episode 10: Beautiful Flower"